

About Me

I am a student currently pursuing my education at Muhammadiyah University Malang. I have knowledge in various programming languages, databases, and design. As an individual, I possess skills in both independent and collaborative work, and I have a 3-month internship experience in the field of IT Support.

Expertise Skill

- Computer Programing
- Design Skills
- Problem Solving
- Interpersonal Skills
- Teamwork

Contact Me

- 0812-4333-1933
- Mahyupra03@gmail.com
- Karangploso, Malang, East Java 65152

Wahyu Pramana Putra

Education

- TELKOM Vocational High School
 Banjarbaru
 Department of Computer and
 Network Engineering (2017 2020)
- University of Muhammadiyah
 Malang
 Informatics (2020 Present)

Work Experience

- PT. PLN (Persero) Wilayah Kalimantan
 Selatan dan Kalimantan Tengah
 IT Support | 2019
 - Web Design
 - Resolve network issues such as internet connectivity, local network, and other network problems.
 - Ensure the availability of computer networks and stable systems.
 - Hardware and software installation and configuration
 - Perform installation, configuration, maintenance, and updates of computer hardware and software.
 - Provide basic training to users on software, hardware and best practices in the use of IT systems.



DWIKI MAULANA SUHARTO

INFORMATICS ENGINEERING

CONTACT

- +62 857-4861-0967
- dwikimaulana6701@gmail.com
- Oau, Malang, East Java 65151
- dwikimaulana6701_

EDUCATION

SMAN 1 Krembung

Science Major (2017 - 2020)

University of Muhammadiyah Malang

Informatics Engineering 2020 - Present

SKILLS

- Computer Programing
- Design Skills
- Teamwork
- Management Skills
- · Interpersonal Skills
- Communication
- Friendly

ABOUT ME

I am student of Informatics at University of Muhammadiyah Malang, with a basic understanding of programming languages, basic database concepts, and design. Additionally, I have the ability to work effectively both in a team and individually, and I have good time management skills.

EXPERIENCE

- Chairman of the IPNU Organization (2021-2022)
- Participant of Short Course CoE at the UMM: Culture of innovation organized by AWS Academy (2022)
 - Develop the ability to think critically, innovatively and solutive about the problems that occur.
 - Cloud technology learning (Amazon Web Service)
- Participant of Laravel Web Development Bootcamp from SanberCode (2022)
 - Web Design
 - · Database MySql Basic
 - · Collaborate with the team via githubt, etc

SOFTWARE

- Visual Studio Code
- Figma
- Xampp
- Whimsical
- Arduino IDF



PROFILE

I am an informatics student at the University of Muhammadiyah Malang, have experience in school and campus organizations, have a basic understanding of programming languages, databases, and design. Besides that, I have good time management skills and I have the ability to work in a team or individually

SKILL

- Teamwork
- UI/UX Design
- Management skilss
- Copywriting
- Figma
- Canva
- Computer Programming

EDUCATION

• Department Of Multimedia

SMK Modern Al-Rifa'ie 2018 - 2020

Informatics

University of Muhammadiyah Malang 2020 - Present

ADITYA FATHUR RAHMAN

Informatics Engineering

- 081334879180
- adityafathurrahman14@gmail.com
- JI.Tirto Utomo Gang.8 Nomor.4 Kec.Dau Kab.Malang

WORK EXPERIENCE

Member of the community social division

Informatics Student Association University of Muhammadiyah Malang (2022)

- Working together as a team
 Organizing Social and Service
 Activities To the Community So that the Creation and Formation One of the Tri Dharma of Higher Education is Service To Society
- Synergize And Harmonize All Elements That Are In UM Informatics

SOFWARE

- visual Studio Code
- Figma
- Xamp
- Whimsical

Pringgo Arif Himantoro

"I am a student of Informatics at University of Muhammadivah Malang, with a basic understanding of programming languages, databases, and design. Additionally, I possess the ability to work both in teams and individually, and I have good time management skills."





EXPERIENCE

· Member of the Entrepreneurship Division

Informatics Student Association, University of Muhammadiyah Malang

- · Developed and executed social media account strategies for the Entrepreneurship Division (KWU)
- Promoted and sold Informatics UMM products and merchandise
- · Collaborated with the Informatics Student Association's social media accounts to promote products and merchandise





LAST EDUCATION

· Department of Mathematics and Sciences

SMA Negeri 1 Penajam Paser Utara

2017 - 2020

Informatics

University of Muhammadiyah Malang

2020 - Present



SKILLS

- · Computer Programing
- UI Design
- Copywriting
- Management Skills
- Teamwork



SOFTWARE

- Visual Studio Code
- Figma
- Whimsical
- · XAMPP



CONTACT DETAILS



pringgo25@gmail.com



081275330591



Karangploso, Malang, East Java 65152